EDWIN KANYOTU

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER/ARCHITECT

PROFILE

Software Developer with 2+ years of experience. Excellent problem-solving skills, teamwork ethic, interpersonal skills, self-motivation and hard-work. Have very good implementation knowledge of OOPs and collection frameworks, APIs and databases. Ready to engage on a steep learning curve, be proactive, have a desire to learn and a drive to keep innovating.

CONTACT

+254724358170

eddykanyz.ek@gmail.com

Nairobi, Kenya

https://www.linkedin.com/in/edwinkanyotu-aa99b8128/

WORK DONE

Website

:https://official-portfolio-tau.vercel.a
pp/

Github

https://github.com/Eddychase

EDUCATION

2015-2021

ARCHITECTURE

JOMO KENYATTA UNIVERSITY OF AGRICULTURE AND TECHNOLOGY

- Nairobi, Kenya

2020-2021

WEB DEVELOPMENT

Moringa School

FRONTEND SKILLS

- React
- Angular
- Vue

BACKEND SKILLS

- Python
- Flask

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Tripitaca - Nairobi September 2021 – December 2021

- Analyzed user needs and proposed design software solutions to meet them.
- Deployed and integrated software engineered by the team
- Updated integration/deployment scripts to improve continuous integration practices.
- Collaborated closely with the team to generate front-end design code.

ARCHITECT ASSOCIATE

Spaceline Design Ltd, - Nairobi, Kenya May 2020 - Sep 2020

- Assisted with all phases of design for concepts through construction document preparation.
- Produced working drawings such as site plans, floor plans, building sections, and interior/ exterior elevations with BIM technology.
- Visited worksites for onsite management.

INTERN ARCHITECT

Spaceline Design Ltd, - Nairobi, Kenya May 2019 - Sep 2019

- Planning diagrams/layouts during schematic design, demonstrating ability to arrange a unified design.
- Research the different types of building materials, lighting fixtures and other products.
- Assisting in the preparation of studies and reports.

Django		